

A Medical Office Specialist with five years of experience within the healthcare industry, specializing in office administration, appointment scheduling, EHR, and HI PAA regulations. A strong history of coordinating with physicians, nurses, and office personnel to identify opportunities to improve office operations.

**Professional Experience** 

## Medical Office Specialist

Penn Medicine Doctor's Office, Media, PA | October 2016 - Present

- Oversee daily appointment scheduling for medical office with 30+ patients per day, manage calendars for physicians, and interface with patients to perform initial interviews, gather medical data, and obtain insurance information
- Coordinate with the office team to implement a new patient records system to reduce data entry time for medical reports from 25 minutes to five minutes
- Reduce outstanding payments for services by 15% by contacting delinquent accounts to create payment plans prior to transferring to collections

## Medical Office Specialist

Office of Dr. Marcus Crowell, Philadelphia, PA | May 2011 - October 2016

- Managed daily calendars and schedules for three physicians, conducted patient intake, created patient files, and processed co-pays and insurance payments
- Supported theoffice in transitioning over 500+ patient files from a paper-based system to a digital record-keeping system to reduce office supply costs

123 Carpenter Street, Philadelphia PA, 12345 m e I issaanderso n@exam ple.com {123} 456-7390

## Education

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.)
Communication
Temple University, Philadelphia, PA
September 2007 - May 2011

## **Key Skills**

- ♦ Calendar Management
- ♦ Office Management
- · Appointment Scheduling
- Electronic Medical Records (EHR)
- Process Improvement